Guide to the Herman Haupt Chapman Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- CORRESPONDENCE AND TOPICAL FILES, 1897-1963; Series II; 16 linear feet (39 boxes)
  - Fire, 1940-1950
    - May, Ben (Box 66, Folder 404)
    - Morris, D. J. (Box 66, Folder 405)
    - Opinions (Box 66, Folder 406)
    - Organizations (Box 66, Folder 407)
    - Ottmeier, William (Box 66, Folder 408)
    - Pessin, L. J. (Box 66, Folder 409)
    - Seigworth, Kenneth J. (Box 66, Folder 410)
    - Simerly, N. G. T. (Box 66, Folder 411)
    - Sonderegger, Ult (Box 66, Folder 412)
    - Southern Yield tables (Box 66, Folder 413)
    - Stoddard area (Box 66, Folder 414)
    - Terry, Elwood (Box 66, Folder 415)
    - Wahlenberg, W. G. (Box 66, Folder 416)
    - Watts, Lyle H. (Box 66, Folder 417)
    - Westveld, R. H. (Box 66, Folder 418)
    - Wheeler, H. N. (Box 66, Folder 419)
    - Wirt, George (Box 66, Folder 420)
  - Fire damage, 1920-1938 (Box 66, Folder 421-422)
    See also: box 84, folder 841
  - Fire fighting equipment, 1925-1931 (Box 67, Folder 423-425)
  - Forest Conservation Society, 1953 (Box 67, Folder 426)
  - Forest Farmers Association, 1950 (Box 67, Folder 427)
  - Forest finance
    See: box 58, folder 299 box 61, folder 345 box 68, folder 448 box 69, folder 476 box 90, folders 974-982
  - Forest fires, 1920-1955
    - Administration (Box 67, Folder 428-429)
    - Causes (Box 67, Folder 430)
    - Enforcement: legal (Box 67, Folder 431)
    - Firefighting (Box 67, Folder 432)
    - History (Box 67, Folder 433-434)
    - Prevention (Box 67, Folder 435)
    - Public relations (Box 67, Folder 436)
  - Forest History Foundation, 1953-1958 (Box 67, Folder 437)
  - Forest homesteads, 1910-1925 (Box 67, Folder 438)
  - Forest insects, 1928-1956 (Box 67, Folder 439)
  - Forest Management, 1931-1957 (Box 68, Folder 440-443)
  - Forest Mensuration, 1914-1956 (Box 68, Folder 444-445)
  - Forest practices survey report, 1946-1952 (Box 68, Folder 446-447)
  - Forest rent versus soil rent, undated (Box 68, Folder 448)
  - Forest resources as a source of employment, 1935 (Box 68, Folder 449)
  - Forest Service, 1932-1959
    See also: box 68, folder 446
    - General (Box 68, Folder 450-452)
    - Appointments (Box 68, Folder 453)
    - Mining claims (Box 68, Folder 454)
    - Policies (Box 68, Folder 455)
    - Revenues (Box 68, Folder 456)
  - Forest supervision, 1936 (Box 68, Folder 457)
  - Forest survey methods, 1912-1923 (Box 68, Folder 458)
  - Forest survey, national, 1931 (Box 68, Folder 459)
  - Forest taxation, 1923-1932 (Box 68, Folder 460-463)
  - Forest Valuation, 1941-1956 (Box 69, Folder 464-465)
  - "The Forester", 1931 (Box 69, Folder 466)
  - Foresters for Conservation, 1956-1957 (Box 69, Folder 467)
  - Forestry in Foreign Countries, 1921-1935 (Box 69, Folder 468-469)
  - Forestry school heads, undated (Box 69, Folder 470)
  - G, 1940-1959 (Box 69, Folder 471)
  - Gaensehals, Frank, 1951 (Box 69, Folder 472)
  - Gaines, Edward M., 1947 (Box 69, Folder 473)
  - Garratt, George A., 1956 (Box 69, Folder 474)
  - Gaylord Container Corporation, 1950-1959 (Box 69, Folder 475)
  - General rental formulas, 1937 (Box 69, Folder 476)
  - Geology, undated (Box 69, Folder 477)
  - Gevorkiantz, S. R., 1938-1948 (Box 69, Folder 478-479)
    See also: box 79, folder 743
  - Gianella, Bill, 1951 (Box 69, Folder 480)
  - Girard, James W., 1933-1938 (Box 69, Folder 481)
  - Grand Rapids, Minnesota, 1945-1962
    - General (Box 69, Folder 482-483)
    - Core samples (Box 69, Folder 484)
    - Pine plantations (Box 69, Folder 485-486)
    - Plantations (Box 69, Folder 487)
  - Graves, Henry Solon, 1950-1952 (Box 69, Folder 488)
  - Grazing, 1928, 1941, undated (Box 69, Folder 489)
  - "The Great Principle", undated (Box 70, Folder 490)
  - H, 1914-1961 (Box 70, Folder 491-492)
  - Hall, R. C., 1946 (Box 70, Folder 493)
  - Haupt, Kathryn, undated (Box 70, Folder 494)
  - Hess, Julia, 1921 (Box 70, Folder 495)
  - Heyward, Frank Jr., 1941, 1950 (Box 70, Folder 496)
  - Hiley, W. H., 1928-1929 (Box 70, Folder 497)
  - Hine, William, 1931-1953 (Box 70, Folder 498)
  - Hogs, 1941 (Box 70, Folder 499)
  - Horizontal cut, 1939-1940 (Box 70, Folder 500)
  - House, William P., 1950-1951 (Box 70, Folder 501)
  - House Resolution 2296, 1949 (Box 70, Folder 502)
  - Humbert, Paul, 1926 (Box 70, Folder 503)
  - Humphrey, M. W., 1946-1947 (Box 70, Folder 504)
  - Incremental hammer, undated (Box 70, Folder 505)
  - Insect control methods, undated (Box 70, Folder 506)
  - "Integrity", undated (Box 70, Folder 507)
  - International Lumber Company, 1925, 1942 (Box 70, Folder 508)
  - International Paper Company, 1948-1952 (Box 70, Folder 509)
  - International Society of Tropical Foresters, 1951-1962 (Box 70, Folder 510)
  - Jack pine reproduction, 1948 (Box 70, Folder 511)
  - Jackson Lumber Company, 1945-1951, undated (Box 70, Folder 512-514)
  - Jewitt, George Frederick, 1951, 1952 (Box 70, Folder 515)
  - Johnson, Bud, 1944 (Box 70, Folder 516)
  - Johnston, Don, 1942-1951 (Box 70, Folder 517)
  - Journal of Forestry, 1948-1960 (Box 70, Folder 518)
  - Kaplan, J. S., 1921, 1963 (Box 71, Folder 519)
  - Kaufert, F. H., 1950-1956 (Box 71, Folder 520)
  - Kaul, Hugh, 1950 (Box 71, Folder 521)
  - Kaul Lumber Company, 1950, undated (Box 71, Folder 522)
  - Kaul report, 1908, 1950 (Box 71, Folder 523)
  - Kelso, Elmer G., 1950, 1951 (Box 71, Folder 524)
  - Kienholz, Raymond, 1951, 1952 (Box 71, Folder 525)
  - Kinney, J. P., 1956 (Box 71, Folder 526)
  - Koroleff, A., 1953, 1954, undated (Box 71, Folder 527)
  - Korstian, C. F., 1957 (Box 71, Folder 528)
  - Krauch, Herman, 1935, 1956, undated (Box 71, Folder 529)
  - Labor relations, 1943 (Box 71, Folder 530)
  - Lamb, Frank H., 1949 (Box 71, Folder 531)
  - Land classification, 1908-1915 (Box 71, Folder 532)
  - Land clearing, undated (Box 71, Folder 533)
  - Land exchange, undated (Box 71, Folder 534)
  - Land settlement, 1911-1912 (Box 71, Folder 535)
  - Lang, Duncan M., 1947, 1958 (Box 71, Folder 536)
  - Larsen, C. Syrach, 1949, 1953 (Box 71, Folder 537)
  - Larsen, J. A., 1959 (Box 71, Folder 538)
  - Lectures
    - "Function of Independent Observations", undated (Box 71, Folder 539)
    - "Multiple Use", undated (Box 71, Folder 540)
    - Outlines, undated (Box 71, Folder 541)
  - Lee, Laurence F., 1953 (Box 71, Folder 542)
  - LeMieux, Frank J., 1948, 1951 (Box 71, Folder 543)
    See also: box 74, folders 611-613
  - LeMieux, Fred, 1953 (Box 71, Folder 544)
    See also: box 82, folder 808
  - Liggett, Walter, 1951 (Box 71, Folder 545)
  - Liming, Franklin G., 1951 (Box 71, Folder 546)
  - Lin, D. Y., 1950 (Box 71, Folder 547)
  - Licensing of foresters, 1937-1950 (Box 71, Folder 548-549)
  - Loblolly pine yield tables, undated (Box 71, Folder 550)
    See also: box 59, folders 314-316 box 61, folder 358 box 78, folders 713-714
  - Log rules, 1900-1958 (Box 72, Folder 551-566)
  - Longleaf pine seed study, 1914-1948 (Box 72, Folder 551-566)
    See also: box 55, folder 227 box 56, folder 230 box 56, folder 243 box 58, folder 280 box 58, folder 300 box 89, folder 959
    - Conclusions (Box 73, Folder 567)
    - Cone tree seed yield (Box 73, Folder 568-569)
    - Data (Box 73, Folder 570)
    - Decadence (Box 73, Folder 571)
    - Deterioration (Box 73, Folder 572)
    - Fire effects (Box 73, Folder 573)
    - Fire resistance study (Box 73, Folder 574)
    - Germination percentages (Box 73, Folder 575)
    - Mortality (Box 73, Folder 576)
    - Neal Lumber Company (Box 73, Folder 577)
    - Old timber mortality (Box 73, Folder 578)
    - Records (Box 73, Folder 579)
    - Reproduction study (Box 73, Folder 580-581)
    - Robins (Box 73, Folder 582)
    - Seed crop data (Box 73, Folder 583-584)
    - Seed production data (Box 73, Folder 585-588)
    - Seed tabulation (Box 74, Folder 589)
    - Seed yield (Box 74, Folder 590)
    - Seedlings (Box 74, Folder 591-592)
    - Selective cutting (Box 74, Folder 593)
    - Sheep and cattle damage (Box 74, Folder 594)
    - Shortleaf pine: data (Box 74, Folder 595)
    - Student studies (Box 74, Folder 596)
    - Tree growth (Box 74, Folder 597)
  - Louisiana Forestry Association, 1956 (Box 74, Folder 598)
  - Lumber Manufacturers Association, undated (Box 74, Folder 599)
  - Lutcher and Moore Lumber Company, 1949 (Box 74, Folder 600)
  - Luther plots: volume tables, 1954 (Box 74, Folder 601)
  - Luther sample plots, 1946-1954 (Box 74, Folder 602)
  - Luther woods, 1954-1956 (Box 74, Folder 603-605)
  - M, 1947-1948 (Box 74, Folder 606)
  - MacKaye, Benton, 1948, undated (Box 74, Folder 607)
  - MacMillan, H. R., 1949-1951 (Box 74, Folder 608)
  - McArdle, 1952 (Box 74, Folder 609)
  - McGraw-Hill, undated (Box 74, Folder 610)
  - McMillan, Ed Leigh, 1948-1957, undated (Box 74, Folder 611-612)
  - McMillan Trust, 1951, undated (Box 74, Folder 613)
  - Maher, J. Bysshe, 1952 (Box 74, Folder 614)
  - Maine rule: volume table, undated (Box 74, Folder 615)
  - The Making of a Forester, undated (Box 75, Folder 616-624)
  - Management, 1923-1944 (Box 75, Folder 625)
  - "Management of Baxter State Park...", undated (Box 75, Folder 626)
  - Maps, 1904, undated (Box 75, Folder 627-629)
  - Marking estimates, 1940 (Box 76, Folder 630)
  - Marsh, Raymond E., 1953, 1955, undated (Box 76, Folder 631)
  - Mason, David T., 1953 (Box 76, Folder 632)
  - Mason, E. G., 1947 (Box 76, Folder 633)
  - Masonite Corporation, undated (Box 76, Folder 634)
  - Maxwell, George H., 1959 (Box 76, Folder 635)
  - May, Ben, 1931-1934 (Box 76, Folder 636)
    See also: box 66, folder 404
  - Menominee Indian nation, undated (Box 76, Folder 637)
  - Mesavage, Clement, 1951 (Box 76, Folder 638)
  - Meyer, H. Arthur, 1943, 1952, undated (Box 76, Folder 639)
  - Meyer, Walter H., 1932-1942 (Box 76, Folder 640)
  - Michigan: registered foresters, 1957 (Box 76, Folder 641)
  - Michigan land/economic survey, 1923 (Box 76, Folder 642)
  - T.R. Miller Company, 1948-1951, undated (Box 76, Folder 643)
  - Mine timbers, 1916-1917 (Box 76, Folder 644)
  - Minnesota forestry, 1910-1957 (Box 76, Folder 645)
  - Minnesota logging industry, 1948-1952 (Box 76, Folder 646)
  - Missouri Forest Crop Law, 1946 (Box 76, Folder 647)
  - Mitchell, Harold L., 1952 (Box 76, Folder 648)
    See also: box 60, folder 326
  - Moir, Stuart, 1953 (Box 76, Folder 649)
  - Monahan, Robert S., 1949 (Box 76, Folder 650)
  - Monell, George R., 1956, 1957 (Box 76, Folder 651-652)
  - Moore, A. G. T., 1948 (Box 76, Folder 653)
  - Moore, Ellwood B., 1956 (Box 76, Folder 654)
  - Moore, Robert H., 1934-1956, undated (Box 76, Folder 655-656)
  - Morris, William, 1946 (Box 76, Folder 657)
  - Mulford, Walter, 1947 (Box 76, Folder 658)
  - Munger, Thornton T., 1953 (Box 76, Folder 659)
  - Murie, Olaus J., 1950 (Box 76, Folder 660)
  - National Distillers Products Corporation
    See also: box 77, folder 687 box 91, folder 994
    - General, 1950-1955, undated (Box 76, Folder 661-662)
    - Brown, Thomas F., 1951 (Box 76, Folder 663)
    - Contract, 1951 (Box 76, Folder 664)
    - Report, 1951 (Box 76, Folder 665)
  - National Forestry Conference, 1936 (Box 77, Folder 666)
  - National Lumber Manufacturers Association, undated (Box 77, Folder 667)
    See also: box 77, folder 669
  - National Parks Association, 1958-1959 (Box 77, Folder 668)
  - National Recovery Administration, 1933 (Box 77, Folder 669)
  - National Resources Information Committee, 1953-1955 (Box 77, Folder 670)
  - National Wildlife Federation, 1941-1958 (Box 77, Folder 671)
  - Neal Lumber and Manufacturing Company, 1951, 1952 (Box 77, Folder 672)
  - New England, undated (Box 77, Folder 673)
  - New England Council, 1953 (Box 77, Folder 674)
  - New Zealand, 1949-1960
    - General (Box 77, Folder 675)
    - Clippings (Box 77, Folder 676-677)
    - Lecture and diary notes (Box 77, Folder 678)
    - Photographs and negatives (Box 77, Folder 679-680)
    - Smith, C. M. (Box 77, Folder 681)
  - New Zealand Institute of Foresters, 1945-1959 (Box 77, Folder 682)
  - Newsweek, 1951 (Box 77, Folder 683)
  - Northeast: farm woodlands, 1945-1950 (Box 77, Folder 684)
  - Northeast Pulpwood Research Center
    See: box 68, folders 446-447 box 78, folder 707
  - Northeastern Regional Committee, 1942 (Box 77, Folder 685)
  - Northeastern Resources Committee, 1958 (Box 77, Folder 686)
  - Notes, 1951 (Box 77, Folder 687)
  - Nyce, George M., 1909 (Box 77, Folder 688)
  - Oak wilt, undated (Box 78, Folder 689)
  - Oettmeier, W. M., 1947 (Box 78, Folder 690)
  - Oregon and California Railroad: land claims, 1944-1954, undated (Box 78, Folder 691-694)
  - Osborne, Fairfield, 1949 (Box 78, Folder 695)
  - Over run, 1946 (Box 78, Folder 696)
    See also: box 80, folder 747
  - Ozark soil, 1951 (Box 78, Folder 697)
  - Palestine, undated (Box 78, Folder 698)
  - Parker, William James, 1948-1951 (Box 78, Folder 699)
  - Peck, Allen Steele, 1949 (Box 78, Folder 700)
  - Pennsylvania, 1950-1951
    - Agricultural land (Box 78, Folder 701)
    - Paper companies (Box 78, Folder 702)
    - Production (Box 78, Folder 703)
    - Reforesting (Box 78, Folder 704)
  - Pennsylvania survey, 1949-1952 (Box 78, Folder 705)
  - Permit: Connecticut State Board of Fisheries and Game, undated (Box 78, Folder 706)
  - Philbrook, Douglas A., 1951-1952 (Box 78, Folder 707)
  - Philippines, 1953 (Box 78, Folder 708)
  - Pierson, Henry B., 1956 (Box 78, Folder 709)
  - Pinchot, Gifford, undated (Box 78, Folder 710)
  - Pingree formula, 1943 (Box 78, Folder 711)
  - Pioneer land and timber, 1950 (Box 78, Folder 712)
  - Plot tables, undated (Box 78, Folder 713)
  - Plot yields, undated (Box 78, Folder 714)
  - Pollution, 1945 (Box 78, Folder 715)
  - Pomeroy and McGowin, 1938, 1948, undated (Box 78, Folder 716)
  - Prescribed burning, 1933-1955 (Box 79, Folder 717)
  - Preston, John F., 1951 (Box 79, Folder 718)
  - Professional societies, 1934-1939 (Box 79, Folder 719-720)
  - Publicity, 1951 (Box 79, Folder 721)
  - Pulp paper, 1956 (Box 79, Folder 722)
  - Pulpwood measurement, 1916-1946 (Box 79, Folder 723)
  - Pulpwood statistics, 1948 (Box 79, Folder 724)
  - Quetico-Superior Wilderness Project, 1943-1945 (Box 79, Folder 725)
  - Raindrop splash, 1947 (Box 79, Folder 726)
  - Rainfall, undated (Box 79, Folder 727-728)
  - Randles, Quincy and Katharine, 1924, 1926, 1940, undated (Box 79, Folder 729)
  - Rations, 1912-1923 (Box 79, Folder 730)
  - Read, A. D., 1949 (Box 79, Folder 731)
  - Record, S. J., 1931 (Box 79, Folder 732)
  - References, undated (Box 79, Folder 733)
  - Rhode Island sheets, 1950 (Box 79, Folder 734)
  - Riebold, R. J., 1951 (Box 79, Folder 735)
  - Rockland Light and Power, 1957, undated (Box 79, Folder 736)
  - Rodgers, Andrew D., Ill, 1951 (Box 79, Folder 737)
  - Rosecrans, W. S., 1945 (Box 79, Folder 738)
  - Rotary club, 1957, 1958 (Box 79, Folder 739)
  - Roth, Filibert, 1911, 1955 (Box 79, Folder 740)
  - Royal English Forestry Society, 1934, 1936 (Box 79, Folder 741)
  - St. Regis Paper Company, 1951, 1952, 1957 (Box 79, Folder 742)
  - Sample scaling, 1943, 1945 (Box 79, Folder 743)
  - Satilla Forest, Woodbine, Georgia, 1932, 1950 (Box 79, Folder 744)
  - Save the Redwoods League, 1958 (Box 79, Folder 745)
  - Scaling, 1916-1943 (Box 80, Folder 746-750)
    See also: box 59, folder 318 box 78, folder 696 box 79, folder 743 box 84, folder 845
  - Schaeffer, Walter H., 1955 (Box 80, Folder 751)
  - Schenck, C. A., 1950 (Box 80, Folder 752)
  - Schiff, Ashley L., 1925, 1958, undated (Box 80, Folder 753-754)
  - Schlich, W., 1925 (Box 80, Folder 755)
  - Schmitz, Henry, 1943-1957 (Box 80, Folder 756)
  - Schools
    - Accreditation, 1947-1954 (Box 80, Folder 757-760)
      See also: box 58, folder 290
    - Clepper, Henry, 1948 (Box 80, Folder 761)
    - Harvard University, 1950 (Box 80, Folder 762)
    - University of Minnesota, 1951-1959 (Box 80, Folder 763)
  - Schulman, Edmund, 1955 (Box 80, Folder 764)
  - Scofield, C. S., 1951 (Box 80, Folder 765)
  - Sears, Paul B., 1952, undated (Box 80, Folder 766)
  - Seed distribution, 1932, 1948 (Box 80, Folder 767)
  - Seed trees, undated (Box 80, Folder 768-772)
  - "Seed Trees in Longleaf Pine", 1923, undated (Box 81, Folder 773-774)
  - Seed trees lumber tally, 1937 (Box 81, Folder 775)
  - Seeding, undated (Box 81, Folder 776)
  - Selective logging papers, undated (Box 81, Folder 777)
  - Settlers Within Forest Reserves, 1904 (Box 81, Folder 778)
  - "Shall Trees Be Cut?", 1957-1958 (Box 81, Folder 779)
  - Shaud, George, 1947 (Box 81, Folder 780)
  - Shepard, H. B., 1948-1955 (Box 81, Folder 781)
  - Shull, Frederick G., 1955 (Box 81, Folder 782)
  - "Silvicultural Systems", 1948 (Box 81, Folder 783)
  - Silviculture, undated (Box 81, Folder 784-785)
    See also: box 59, folder 312 box 61, folder 361 box 70, folder 505
  - Simmons, C. W., 1952, undated (Box 81, Folder 786)
  - Slash disposal, 1928 (Box 81, Folder 787)
  - Smith, Eastburn R., 1948-1957 (Box 81, Folder 788)
  - Society of American Foresters, 1922-1961
    See also: box 55, folder 214 box 58, folder 290 box 58, folder 299 box 60, folders 329-330 box 69, folder 467 box 69, folder 470 box 70, folder 518 box 71, folder 520 box 71, folder 530 box 78, folders 691-694 box 80, folder 757 box 90, folder 973
    - General (Box 81, Folder 789)
    - Accreditation (Box 81, Folder 790)
      See also: box 80, folders 757-760
    - Advertising (Box 81, Folder 791)
    - Affiliate members (Box 81, Folder 792)
    - Clepper, Henry (Box 81, Folder 793)
      See also: box 80, folder 761
    - Committee on Ethics (Box 81, Folder 794)
    - Committee on Standards (Box 81, Folder 795)
    - Convention (Box 81, Folder 796)
    - Council meeting minutes (Box 81, Folder 797)
    - Council political activity (Box 81, Folder 798)
    - Council report (Box 82, Folder 799)
    - Diller case (Box 82, Folder 800)
    - Drake, George L. (President) (Box 82, Folder 801)
    - Elections (Box 82, Folder 802)
    - Ethics: Recknagel case (Box 82, Folder 803)
    - Fellows (Box 82, Folder 804-805)
    - Greeley Committee (Box 82, Folder 806)
    - Historical summary (Box 82, Folder 807)
    - LeMieux, Fred (Box 82, Folder 808)
    - Martin, Clyde S. (President) (Box 82, Folder 809-810)
    - Membership drive (Box 82, Folder 811)
    - Murphy, Louis: Hare system (Box 82, Folder 812)
    - National meeting: Programs (Box 82, Folder 813)
    - New England Section: general (Box 82, Folder 814-816)
    - New England Section:
      - General (Box 83, Folder 817-818)
      - Allegheny Section case (Box 83, Folder 819)
      - Bylaws (Box 83, Folder 820)
      - Code of Ethics (Box 83, Folder 821)
      - Committee on Forest Policy (Box 83, Folder 822)
      - Committee on Improvement of Stands (Box 83, Folder 823)
      - Disciplinary action procedure (Box 83, Folder 824)
      - LeMieux article (Box 83, Folder 825)
      - Meetings (Box 83, Folder 826)
      - Professional Standards Committee (Box 83, Folder 827)
      - Yale Library (Box 83, Folder 828)
    - Objectives (Box 83, Folder 829)
    - Officers (Box 83, Folder 830)
    - Pamphlets (Box 83, Folder 831)
    - Policies (Box 83, Folder 832)
    - Referenda (Box 84, Folder 833-834)
    - Remittance of dues (Box 84, Folder 835)
    - Reprints from Journal of Forestry (Box 84, Folder 836)
    - Section manual (Box 84, Folder 837)
    - Student Member Program (Box 84, Folder 838)
    - Miscellanea (Box 84, Folder 839)
  - Somers, Gayle H., 1953, undated (Box 84, Folder 840)
  - Southern fires, 1945 (Box 84, Folder 841)
  - Southern pine plots, 1957 (Box 84, Folder 842)
  - Spurr, Stephen H., 1950-1956 (Box 84, Folder 843)
  - "Stand Density Index. Reineke.", 1947 (Box 84, Folder 844)
  - Standardization: volume tables, 1925 (Box 84, Folder 845)
  - Stassen, Harold E., 1948, undated (Box 84, Folder 846)
  - States, 1950-1956
    - Connecticut (Box 84, Folder 847-849)
    - Economics (Box 84, Folder 850)
    - Forestry agencies (Box 84, Folder 851)
    - Labor policies (Box 84, Folder 852)
    - Ohio (Box 84, Folder 853)
    - Organizations (Box 84, Folder 854)
    - Pennsylvania (Box 85, Folder 855-859)
    - Rhode Island (Box 85, Folder 860)
    - Utilization (Box 85, Folder 861)
  - Stem analysis, 1916-1922 (Box 85, Folder 862)
  - Stetson, Irving G., 1956 (Box 85, Folder 863)
  - Stimpson, F. T., 1953 (Box 85, Folder 864)
  - Stott, C. B.: tree grade, undated (Box 85, Folder 865)
  - Strickland, Sam, 1949 (Box 85, Folder 866)
  - Swedish forest formula, 1950 (Box 85, Folder 867)
  - Swift, Ernest, 1957 (Box 85, Folder 868)
  - Tanbark, 1916 (Box 85, Folder 869)
  - Tannehill, G. F., 1948-1957 (Box 85, Folder 870)
  - Teapot Dome, 1958 (Box 85, Folder 871)
  - Tebbe, Charles L., 1952, 1955 (Box 85, Folder 872)
  - Technology, n.a. (Box 85, Folder 873)
  - Thinning, 1948-1958 (Box 85, Folder 874-875)
    See also:. box 58, folder 282
  - Thinning plots, undated (Box 85, Folder 876-877)
  - Thinning versus pulpwood, 1955 (Box 85, Folder 878)
  - "Thoughts on Living", undated (Box 85, Folder 879-880)
  - Timber estimating, 1909-1939 (Box 86, Folder 881-886)
  - Timber resources report, 1947 (Box 86, Folder 887)
  - Toomey, Edmond G., 1951 (Box 86, Folder 888)
  - Topography, 1937-1951 (Box 86, Folder 889)
  - Toumey, James W., 1921, 1932, undated (Box 86, Folder 890)
  - Tree diseases, undated (Box 86, Folder 891)
  - Tree farming, 1957-1962 (Box 86, Folder 892-893)
  - Tree rings, 1935-1936 (Box 86, Folder 894)
  - Tryon, Henry H., 1949, 1952 (Box 86, Folder 895)
  - Union of Protestant sects, 1955-1957 (Box 87, Folder 896)
  - Urania, Louisiana, [ca. 1921-1951]
    See also: box 76, folder 630 box 79, folder 727 box 81, folders 773-775 box 81, folder 787 box 85, folder 870
    - General (Box 87, Folder 897-899)
    - Bickford, California: report on Chapman Forest (Box 87, Folder 900)
    - Blackwell, Lloyd P. (Box 87, Folder 901-902)
    - Charts and instructions (Box 87, Folder 903)
    - Correspondence (Box 87, Folder 904)
    - Crown heights (Box 87, Folder 905)
    - Diameter growth data (Box 87, Folder 906)
    - Elk Pasture (Box 87)
    - Experiments (Box 87, Folder 911)
    - Field trip guides (Box 87, Folder 912-913)
      See also: box 66, folder 396
    - Figures (Box 87, Folder 914)
    - Fire project (Box 87, Folder 915)
    - Forum of record for longleaf seedling plots (Box 87, Folder 916)
    - Frost damage (Box 87, Folder 917)
    - General data (Box 87, Folder 918)
    - Greeley Pasture burn (Box 87, Folder 919)
    - Height curves (Box 88, Folder 920)
    - Ice damage (Box 88, Folder 921)
    - Instructions (Box 88, Folder 922)
    - Length of crown versus volume of crown study (Box 88, Folder 923)
    - Longleaf, loblolly competition (Box 88, Folder 924)
    - Longleaf pine
      - Diameter growth data (Box 88, Folder 925)
      - Results (Box 88, Folder 926)
      - Summary (Box 88, Folder 927)
      - Thinning (Box 88, Folder 928-929)
        See also: box 85, folders 874-877
    - Plot crown development (Box 88, Folder 930)
    - Plots: (Box 88)
      See also: box 78, folders 713-714
    - Research article (Box 88, Folder 944)
    - Roberts plot burn (Box 88, Folder 945)
    - Sample tree (Box 89, Folder 946)
    - Schedules (Box 89, Folder 947)
    - Seed trees (Box 89, Folder 948)
      See also: box 80, folders 768-772
    - Selective burning (Box 89, Folder 949)
    - Soil analysis (Box 89, Folder 950)
    - Tables (Box 89, Folder 951)
    - Temperature record (Box 89, Folder 952)
    - Yield tables (Box 89, Folder 953-955)
      See also: box 71, folder 550
    - U.S. Department of the Interior
      See: box 61, folder 341
    - U.S. Forest Service
  - Valhalla, New York, 1953, 1955, undated (Box 89, Folder 956)
  - Valuation of standing timber
    See: box 90, folders 974-982
  - Vancouver, Canada: photographs, [1958?] (Box 89, Folder 957)
  - No folder (Box 89, Folder 958)